

ABOUT ME

Impact-driven product designer with experience in e-commerce, insurtech, and SaaS industry. My passion lies in designing solutions that leave a lasting, postive impact. I strive to tackle any problem with critical thinking and a positive attitude.

TECH SKILLS

DESIGN DEVELOPMENT AND TOOLS RESEARCH TOOLS

Figma HTML/CSS
Figjam Javascript/jQuery
Adobe CC Google Analytics
Principle Git/GitHub
Overflow Hotjar

Maze

COMPETENCIES

Miro

Visual Design Interface Design Interaction Design Experience Design Wireframing Prototyping Design System
Design Heuristics
User Interview
Usability Testing
A/B Testing
Data Analysis

EDUCATION

SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY
B/A - Interactive Arts + Technology
Design Concentration

Graduated with Distinction and Co-op Education Award 2014 - 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

DEAN'S HONOR ROLL FALL 2014

Awarded to students for achieving a 3.50 (out of 4.33) or higher GPA.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Designer / Shopee

JUL - NOV 2022

- Designed intuitive solutions to improve the seller centre and buyer marketplace experience based on the existing regional design system.
- Communicated with cross functional teams to develop solutions, receive feedback, and manage multiple projects in a fast-paced environment.

Senior Product Designer / Tokoplas

SEP 2020 - JUN 2022

- Worked closely with management and engineers to redefine the user experience of the e-commerce website, seller portal, and mobile apps.
- Led the design efforts of the new website and seller portal as well as creating design system, mockups, and prototypes for development.

UI/UX Designer / Zaui Software

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

- Collaborated with engineers and product experts to design flows and features for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Developed wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and interactive prototypes for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.

Digital Designer / PayByPhone

OCT 2018 - APR 2019

- Redefined the user experience and redesigned the interface of the new parking operators (B2B) and careers pages.
- Produced marketing materials for print and digital such as promotional banners, posters, postcards, display ads, and social media graphics.

UI/UX Designer / BSTRO

MAY - SEP 2018

- Collaborated with designers in an agency environment to design digital experiences for J&J, Chef Software, and San Francisco Marathon.
- Day-to-day included creative concepting, competitive analysis, sitemap drafting, wireframing, mockups design, and prototyping.

UI/UX Designer / BuzzIt Inc.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

- Worked collaboratively with a product manager and a developer in redesigning BuzzIt's website and mobile apps in a startup environment.
- Overhauled the visual design and user experience of the entire Android & iOS app by producing 50+ sets of end to end mockups.